A Guide to the Papers of Howard W. Smith, 1933-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V: Speeches, Articles, Recordings, etc.
  - 76th Congress
    - National Labor Relations Board against Sterling electric Motors, Inc. Smith extension of remarks, May 13, 1940 (Box 191)
    - Smith amendments to N.L.R.B., general debate on (green letter), June 6, 1940 (Box 191)
    - "Can the Wagner Act Be Made to Work?", May 9, 1940 (Box 191)
  - 77th Congress
    - Smith proposed amendment to Maritime Bill to prohibit closed shop, general debate, January 24, 1941 (Box 191)
    - Smith proposed amendment to appropriation bill and Woodendrum opposition, [February 27, 1941] (Box 191)
    - Bill to authorize Naval Affairs Committee to investigate war program, debate and vote on (Box 191)
    - H.R. 162 - April 2, 1941 (Box 191)
    - War Department Appropriation Bill - proposed Smith amendment to prohibit strikes and closed shop, debate and vote on, June 1, 1941 (Box 191)
    - May amendment to military affairs bill to limit strikes, pickets, etc., debate and vote on, July 9, 1941 (Box 191)
    - Meutrality Act, speech and opposition to, repealing sections of, November 12, 1941 (opposition used extractws in campaign for Congress) (Box 191)
    - Chamber of Commerce Speech, Burrough of Queens, New York, December 2, 1941 (Box 191)
    - National Association of Manufacturers speech, New York, December 4, 1941 (Box 191)
    - Congressional Record, December 23, 1941, containing "extension of remarks of Hon. Howard W. Smith of Virginia" on "organized labor and the farmers" (Box 191)
    - American Bar Association Journal (January, 1942) included an article by Smith entitled "What Laws Should be Passed to Prevent Strikes in Defense Industries?" (Box 191)
    - War Powers Bill - proposed amendment to suspend 40-hour work week, February 25, 1942 (Box 191)
    - War Powers Bill (2nd) - Smith amendment suspending 40-hour laws. February 26, 1942. (Limiting Treasury and Federal Reserve Board to 5 billion). (Box 191)
    - Congressional Record, February 25, 1942, containing remarks of Smith on H.R. 6616, to suspend the 8-hour laws, etc. (Box 191)
    - Congressional Record, February 26, 1942, containing remarks by Smith concerning a limitation on the amount to be borrowed by the Treasury. (Box 191)
    - Congressional Record, February 27, 1942, containing remarks by Smith onthe 8-hour laws, etc. (Box 191)
    - speech-prepared March 23, 1942, concerning the domestic economy and the war effort (Box 191)
    - Speech (radio), April 11, 1942, entitled "A National Labor Policy" (Box 191)
    - Speech - Chicago National Metal Trades Association, March 25, [1942]. (Box 191)
    - Speech - St. Louis National Metal Trades Association, March 26, 1942. (Box 191)
    - Speech - U.S. Chamber of Commerce, Chicago, Illinois, April 28, 1942 (Box 191)
    - Speech - National Metal Trades Association, Syracuse, New York, April 16, [1942] (Box 191)
    - Speech - N.B.C., "The 40-Hour Week", April 20, 1942 (Box 191)
    - Speech - Illinois Manufacturers Association, Chicago, Illinois, April 21, 1942 (Box 191)
    - Speech - Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce National Affairs Committee, April 22, 1942 (Box 191)
    - Speech - National Metal Trades Association, New York, may 18, 1942 (Box 191)
    - Speech - Campaign Radio Speech, July 30, 1942, WJSV (Box 191)
    - "The Navy's Challenge for Service," speech by the Judge [Smith] on October 2, 1942 (Box 191)
    - The Commonwealth Monitor, July 30, 1938 (Box 191)
    - Congressional Record speeches: (Box 191)
    - April 26, 1933 - Impeachment of Judge Lowell (Box 191)
    - Jan. 23, 1935 - "Unconstitutional Delegation of Legislative (Box 191)
    - June 19, 1935 - "Unconstitutionality of the Wagner-Connery Labor Disputes Bill (Box 191)
    - June 18, 1936 - "Deportation of Criminal Aliens" (Box 191)
    - Aug. 16, 1937 - "Black-Connery Wages and Hours Bill" (Box 191)
    - March 20, 1939 - "Let Us Stamp Out Subversive and Un-American Activities in Our Midst" (Box 191)
    - March 26, 1941 - "Strikes are Sabotage in the Country's Defense Preparations" (Box 191)
  - 78th Congress
    - Speech, Congressional Record, March 12, 1943 re: $25,000 salary limitation (Box 192)
    - speech, Congressional Record, April 12, 1943 re: the Freedom of Jefferson (Box 192)
    - Speech, [ Congressional Record ], May 18, 1944 re: amendment to G.I. bill; also re: political action committee (Box 192)
    - Speech, Town Hall of the Air, May 29, 1943 re: Connery-Smith anti-Strike Bill (Box 192)
    - Speech, [July 18, 1943] re: G.I. bill (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Feb. 3, 1944 re: States rights with respect to suffrage (Box 192)
    - War Powers Bill (2nd) - Smith proposed amendment to suspend 40-hour week, debate on. February 27, 1942, from the Congressional Record (Box 192)
    - Article, Jan. 7, 1944 re: Comment on Donald R. Richberg article - proposals for a new labor policy (Box 192)
    - Speech, radio WMAL-1030-National Forum, Jan. 10, 1944 re: What should be done to prevent wartime strikes? (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, May 5, 1955 re: Montgomery Ward Seizure (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Feb. 2, 1943 re: lack of policy with respect to labor (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Feb. 25, 1943 re: amendment on the National Labor Relations Act (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Feb. 25, 1943 re: on bill to amend National Labor Relations Act (Box 192)
    - Speeches - miscellaneous (Box 192)
  - 79th Congress
    - H.R. 1946 January 15 - Congressional Record (Box 192)
    - H.R. 1946 January 23 - Congressional Record (Box 192)
    - H.R. 1946 February 25 - Congressional Record (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, April 12, 1943, "The Freedoms of Jefferson" (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Jan. 17, 1946, "The Land of the Free???" (Box 192)
    - Speech, Congressional Record, Carpetbaggers' Invasion 1946 Model" (Box 192)
    - H.R. 1946 February 25 - Congressional Record (Box 193)
    - H.R. 1946 January 31 - Congressional Record (Box 193)
    - H.R. 1946 April 30 - Congressional Record (Box 193)
    - Correspondence re: Labor Speeches in House - January 15 & 17, 1946 (Box 193)
    - FEPB speeches (Box 193)
    - Labor speech in House, Jan. 15, 1946 (Box 193)
    - Labor speech in House, Jan. 17, 1946 (Box 193)
    - Army Picket Lines, Speech by Smith, Jan. 23, 1946 (Box 193)
    - Speech on Case Bill, January 31, 1946 (Box 193)
    - Folder of miscellaneous speeches (Box 193)
  - 80th Congress
    - Smith's speeches, 80th Congress, 2nd Session (Box 193)
    - Speech on Marshall Plan and Universal Military training made in House, March 23, 1948 (Box 193)
  - 81st Congress
    - Smith's speeches, 81st Congress - 1st Session (Box 193)
    - "The Kind of Democrat I Am," speech delivered at New York Herald Tribune Forum, Oct. 24, 1949. Inserted in Congressional Record, Jan. 6, 1950 (Box 193)
    - Speech in House on Labor Situation, Feb. 1, 1950 (Box 193)
    - Smith's speeches - 81st Congress (Box 193)
  - 82nd Congress
    - Speech on appropriation for Fish and Wildlife Service, May 2, 1951. (Love-Life of the Racoons) (Box 193)
    - Speech on Armed Forces Pay Increase, Jan. 15, 1952 (Box 193)
    - Speech in House on Allen Resolution and Steel seizure by President, April 24, 1952 (Box 193)
    - Folder containing miscellaneous extra copies of speeches (Box 193)
  - 83rd Congress
    - Speech - "Party Responsibility", April 1, 1953, Congressional Record (Box 193)
    - Smith statement in Federal Aid to Education, n.d. (Box 193)
- Series VI: Campaign Records
  - 1938 Campaign flyer (Box 194)
  - 1942 Campaign, clippings (3 folders) (Box 194)
  - 1942 Campaign, literature (Box 194)
  - 1942 Campaign, speech, radio, July 30 (Box 194)
  - Campaign for 82nd Congress
    - Candidacy papers filed (Box 194)
    - Primary return (primary of August 1, 1950) (Box 194)
    - General Election returns (November 7, 1950) (Box 194)
    - Thank-you letters written after General Election, 1950 (Box 194)
    - Retirement from Congress [letters re contemplated, 1950] (Box 194)
    - Campaign for 82nd Congress - miscellaneous (Box 194)
    - [Letters of] Congratulations on General Election, 1950 (Box 194)
    - Campaign folder [campaign literature, etc.] (Box 194)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 194)
    - Tyrell Krum [Republican opponent], (3 folders) (Box 194)
    - General Election expenses (Box 195)
    - Campaign meetings (Box 195)
    - Primary Expenses (Box 195)
    - Congratulations on renominations in primary (Box 195)
    - Area Folders
      - Arlington (Box 195)
      - Alexandria (Box 195)
      - Albemarle County (Box 195)
      - Charlottesville (Box 195)
      - Fluvanna County (Box 195)
      - Culpeper (Box 195)
      - Falls Church (Box 195)
      - Fairfax County (Box 195)
      - Fauquier County (Box 195)
      - Goochland County (Box 195)
      - King George County (Box 195)
      - Louisa County (Box 195)
      - Loudoun County (Box 195)
      - Madison County (Box 196)
      - Orange County (Box 196)
      - Prince William County (Box 196)
      - Stafford County (Box 196)
    - Eighth District newspapers (Box 196)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 196)
    - Howard W. Smith Advertisements and Campaign Literature, 1950 (Box 196)
    - Arthur F. Souther [Democratic primary opponent] (Box 196)
    - Preachers in 8th District (Box 196)
    - Campaign Expenses, 1950 (Box 196)
    - Releases to Alexandria Gazette (Box 196)
    - Expenses - Convention (Box 196)
    - Election clippings, 1951 (Box 196)
  - Campaign for 83rd Congress
    - Newspaper advertising in 1952 Campaign (Box 196)
    - Campaign folder and Circular letter, Sample Ballot, Misc. Lterature, 1952 Campaign (Box 196)
    - H.R. 8th District Democratic Committee (Box 196)
    - Thank-you letter written after General Election, 1952 (Box 196)
    - Material on Legality of Primary in 1952 (Box 196)
    - Congratulations received after General Election, 1952 (Box 196)
    - Presidential Campaign in 1952 - Stevenson and Eisenhower (Box 196)
    - Returns [1952] (Box 196)
    - Election returns - General Election, 1952 (Box 196)
    - Campaign in 10th District (Box 197)
    - Speech made accepting nomination at convention in Fredericksburg, 10 May 1952 (Box 197)
    - Candidacy papers filed for 83rd Congress (Box 197)
    - Landon Cabell Painter (candidate for Congress - 10th Congressional District - Democrat) (Box 197)
    - Richard L. Feldman (Independent candidate for 10th District) (Box 197)
    - Edmund Campbell (Democratic pirmary candidate) (Box 197)
    - Campaign expenses (Box 197)
    - Letters from Arlington, Alexandria, Fairfax, Falls Church - regarding Judge Smith's departure from that area (Box 197)
    - Homer G. Richey (Independent opponent for 8th District seat) (Box 197)
    - Area Folders
      - Albemarle County, City of Charlottesville (Box 197)
      - Caroline County (Box 197)
      - Culpeper County (Box 197)
      - Fauquier County (Box 197)
      - Fluvanna County (Box 197)
      - Goochland County (Box 197)
      - Greene County (Box 197)
      - Hanover County (Box 197)
      - King George County (Box 197)
      - King William County (Box 197)
      - Lancaster County (Box 197)
      - Loudoun County (Box 197)
      - Louise County (Box 197)
      - Nothumberland County (Box 197)
      - Orange County (Box 197)
      - Prince William County (Box 197)
      - Richmond County (Box 197)
      - Spotsylvania County [and] City of Fredericksburg (Box 197)
      - Stafford County (Box 197)
      - Westmoreland County (Box 197)
    - Senator Byrd - Democratic Pirmary, 1952
    - Newspaper clippings - Byrd Election, 1952 (Box 198)
    - Byrd Campaign, 10th District (Box 198)
      - Byrd Campaign, 1952 - area folders (Box 198)
      - King William, Hanover (Box 198)
      - Orange, Louisa, Green, Goochland (Box 198)
      - Culpeper, Fauquier (Box 198)
      - Caroline, Spotsylvania, Fredericksburg (Box 198)
      - Albemarle, Charlottesville, Fluvanna (Box 198)
      - Lancaster, Westmoreland, Northumberland, Richmond (Box 198)
      - Prince William, Loudoun (Box 198)
      - Stafford, King George (Box 198)
    - Literature of Byrd-Miller Campaign (Box 198)
    - Notices and Resolutions (8th District Convention, Fredericksburg) (Box 198)
  - Campaign for 84th Congress, 1954 (Box 198)
    - Area Folders (Box 198)
      - Charlottesville and Albemarle County (Box 198)
      - Caroline County (Box 198)
      - Culpeper (Box 198)
      - Fredericksburg and Spotsylvania County (Box 198)
      - Fauquier County (Box 198)
      - Louisa, Greene, Orange County (Box 198)
      - Fluvanna and Goochland (Box 198)
      - Hanover and King William (Box 198)
      - Northern Neck (Box 198)
      - Stafford and King George (Box 198)
    - Campaign for 84th Congress - Miscellaneous (Box 198)
    - Election Returns, 1954 (Smith-Lenhart) (Box 199)
    - News Clippings: Smith-Lenhart Campaign, 1954 (Box 199)
    - John Galleher-Senate, 1955 (Box 199)
    - Advertisements and editorials, Smith-Lenhart Campaign, 1954 (Box 199)
    - Campaign Expenses, 1954 (Box 199)
    - Newspaper advertising (Box 199)
    - Edward O. McCue, Jr. - 84th Congress [State Senate campaign] (Box 199)
    - 8th District Convention (Box 199)
    - Democratic Committee Chairmen - 8th Congressional District, 84th Congress (Box 199)
    - John Galleher - [State] Senate 1955 (Box 199)
    - 8th District Democratic Committee, 1955 (Box 199)
  - Campaign for 85th Congress, 1956 (Box 199)
    - H.R. 8th District Convention (Box 199)
    - Area Folders
      - Albemarle County (Box 199)
      - Caroline County (Box 199)
      - City of Fredericksburg (Box 200)
      - City of Charlottesville (Box 200)
      - Culpeper County (Box 200)
      - Fluvanna County (Box 200)
      - Fauquier County (Box 200)
      - Goochland County (Box 200)
      - Greene County (Box 200)
      - Hanover County (Box 200)
      - King George County (Box 200)
      - King William County (Box 200)
      - Lancaster County (Box 200)
      - Loudoun County (Box 200)
      - Louisa County (Box 200)
      - Northumberland County (Box 200)
      - Orange County (Box 200)
      - Prince William County (Box 200)
      - Richmond County (Box 200)
      - Spotsylvania County (Box 200)
      - Stafford County (Box 200)
      - Westmoreland County (Box 200)
    - Expense Account, 1956 Election (Box 200)
    - Campaign literature, clippings, etc. (Box 200)
    - Clippings: Clay-Smith, 1956 (2 folders) (Box 200)
    - Horace E. Clay [Republican opponent] (Box 200)
    - Campaign 1956 (Box 201)
    - Virginia State Convention (July 27, 1956) (Box 201)
    - Democratic National Convention, (1956) (Box 201)
  - Campaign for 86th Congress
    - H.R. 1958 Campaign (Box 201)
    - H.R. 8th District Democratic Dinner, May 25, 1957 (Box 201)
    - J. Lindsay Almond - Gubernatorial Campaign, November 1957 (Box 201)
    - Election returns, November 1957 (Box 201)
    - H.R. 1958 Convention - Fredericksburg, May 10, 1958 (Box 202)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, (Feb. 28, 1958) (Box 202)
    - Material for Key Note Speech at State Democratic Convetion at Virginia Beach, May 21, 1960 (Box 202)
    - Senator Byrd - 1958 Senate Campaign (Box 202)
    - H.R. 1960 Senatorial Campaign (Box 202)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Feb. 19, 1960 (Box 202)
    - General Assembly Dinner, Jan. 20, 1960, given by Judge Smith (Box 202)
  - Campaign for 87th Congress
    - Miscellaneous (Box 202)
    - Area Folders (Box 202)
      - Albemarle County (Box 202)
      - Caroline County (Box 202)
      - Charlottesville City (Box 202)
      - Culpeper County (Box 202)
      - Fauquier County (Box 202)
      - Fredericksburg City (Box 202)
      - Fluvanna County (Box 202)
      - Goochland County (Box 202)
      - Greene County (Box 202)
      - Hanover County (Box 202)
      - King George County (Box 202)
      - King William County (Box 202)
      - Lancaster County (Box 202)
      - Loudoun County (Box 202)
      - Louisa County (Box 202)
      - Northumberland County (Box 202)
      - Orange County (Box 202)
      - Prince William County (Box 202)
      - Richmond County (Box 202)
      - Spotsylvania County (Box 202)
      - Stafford County (Box 202)
      - Westmoreland County (Box 202)
    - Judge Smith's Campaign, 1960 (Box 203)
    - H.R. 1960 Campaign Expenditures (Box 203)
    - H.R. 1960 - 8th District Democratic Convention, April 23, 1960 (Box 203)
    - State Convention - May 21, 1960 (Box 203)
    - Clippings re: Judge Smith's election, November 8, 1960 and presidential election (Box 203)
    - Correspondence between Smith and Robert Kennedy, Sept. 1960 re: remarks made by R.F.K. embarrassing to Judge Smith (Box 203)
    - Letters written to Judge Smith objecting to his non-committal attitude on the Kennedy ticket (November 1960 election) from constituents: [by area]
      - Charlottesville (Box 204)
      - Albemarle County (Box 204)
      - Caroline County (Box 204)
      - Culpeper County (Box 204)
      - Fauquier County (Box 204)
      - City of Fredericksburg (Box 204)
      - Hanover County (Box 204)
      - King George [County] (Box 204)
      - Lancaster County [Northern Neck] (Box 204)
      - Louisa County (Box 204)
      - Loudoun County (Box 204)
      - Orange [County] (Box 204)
      - Prince William County (Box 204)
      - Stafford County (Box 204)
    - 1960 - Campaign File (Robert Kennedy) (Box 204)
    - 1960 Presidential File (Box 204)
    - 1962 Campaign (Box 204)
    - 8th Congressional District Convention, 1962 (Box 204)
    - 1962 Gubernatorial Race (Box 205)
    - 1965 Political - 89th Congress (Box 205)
    - Dinner given by Judge Smith for Legislature, Feb. 25, 1966 (Box 205)
    - Senate Campaign, 1966 (Box 205)
    - Mills E. Godwin, Jr. - Governor, etc. - 89th Congress (Box 205)
    - 1964 Virginia State Convention (Box 205)
    - Flyer letter - 1964 campaign (Box 205)
    - 1964 Campaign (2 folders containing conrrespondence, clippings, etc.) (Box 206)
    - Political correspondence - 88th Congress, 1st Session (Box 206)
    - Kenneth T. Whitescarver (Box 206)
    - H.R. 1964 Presidential Campaign - correpsondence and clippings (Box 207)
    - Political - 88th Congress, 1st Session (Box 207)
    - National Convention, August 1964 (Box 207)
    - Party Plan - 1961 (?) (Box 207)
    - H.R. 1966 Campaign - Form letters and Lists (Box 207)
    - Campaign 1966
  - Campaign 1966 - general material (Box 208)
    - Scott [William L.] - clippings re (Box 208)
    - Caroline (Box 208)
    - Charles City (Box 208)
    - Essex County (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Dranesville District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Lee District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Providence District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Centreville District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Mt. Vernon District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Dranesville, Centreville, Providence District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Lee, Mt. Vernon District (Box 208)
    - Fairfax County-Political (Box 208)
    - Voter's Statistics - Fairfax County (Box 209)
    - Vienna (Box 209)
    - Fauquier (Box 209)
    - Fredericksburg (Box 209)
    - Goochland (Box 209)
    - Hanover (Box 209)
    - King George (Box 209)
    - King & Queen (Box 209)
    - Little Plymouth P.O. (Box 209)
    - King William (Box 209)
    - Lancaster (Box 209)
    - Louisa (Box 209)
    - Loudoun (Box 209)
    - New Kent (Box 210)
    - Northumberland (Box 210)
    - Prince William (Box 210)
    - Richmond (Box 210)
    - Spotsylvania (Box 210)
    - Stafford (Box 210)
    - Westmoreland (Box 210)
    - Press Releases - 1966 Congressional Campaign (Box 210)
    - Declaration of Candidacy, 1966 - Primary, July 12, 1966 (Box 210)
    - Contributions - 1966 (Box 210)
    - Campaign Bills - Primary 1966 (Box 210)
    - Campaign Expenses (Box 210)
    - Budget - Campaign, 1966 (Box 210)
    - Pettit - Talk, Lawson - Talk (Box 210)
    - Ruby Twohy - Precinct Operations (Box 210)
- Series VII: Endorsement and Patronage Correspondence, 83rd-89th Congress
  - A 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - B 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - C 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - D 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - E 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - F 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - G 83rd Congress (Box 211)
  - H 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - I 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - J 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - K 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - L 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - M 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - N 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - O 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - P 83rd Congress (Box 212)
  - Q 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - R 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - S 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - T 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - U 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - V 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - W 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - X, Y, Z 83rd Congress (Box 213)
  - Z 83rd Congress (Box 213)
- Series VIII: Correspondence re Petitions to Qualified Voters
  - Albemarle County and Charlottesville (Box 214)
  - Alexandria (Box 214)
  - Culpeper County (Box 214)
  - Fairfax County and Falls Church (Box 214)
  - Fauquier County (Box 214)
  - Fluvanna County (Box 214)
  - Goochland County (Box 215)
  - Greene County (Box 215)
  - King George County (Box 215)
  - Loudoun County (Box 215)
  - Louisa County (Box 215)
  - Prince William County (Box 215)
  - Madison County (Box 215)
  - Orange County (Box 215)
  - Stafford County (Box 215)
  - Completed (Box 215)
  - Campaign literature (Box 215)
  - Mailing lists - 84th Congress (Box 216)
  - Mailing lists - 84th Congress (?) (Box 217)
  - Omitted (Box 218)
- Series IX: National Labor Relations Board Files
  - Amendments [material re congressional acts re N.L.R.B.] (Box 219)
  - Anonymous [letters re] N.L.R.B. (Box 219)
  - Correspondence with the Labor Board - also re board members (Box 219)
  - Appearances before Committee (Box 219)
  - N.L.R.B. [correspondence] - not worthwhile - junk (Box 219)
  - Commendatory Letters re: Work of Committee (Box 219)
  - Miscellaneous suggestions for N.L.R.B. Amendments (Box 219)
  - Amendments - N.L.R.B. (Box 219)
  - N.L.R.B. - worthwhile - future reference; also vote on bill on floor (Box 219)
  - N.L.R.B. - congratulations from the District; also miscellaneous; also general congratulations (Box 219)
  - Miscellaneous statistics and data (Box 219)
  - Correspondence with colleagues re N.L.R.B. (Box 219)
  - Correspondence with Labor Committee - Mrs. Norton (Box 219)
  - Congratulations re Committee from Constituents, Colleagues, etc. (Box 220)
  - Attorney General's appearance before Committee (Box 220)
  - Conferences - Appointments (Box 220)
  - Correspondence with Ben V. Cohen (Box 220)
  - Correspondence with Minority Members (Box 220)
  - Correspondence with Labor Leaders relative to appearing before Committee, etc. (Box 220)
  - Correspondence with the Attorney General (Box 220)
  - Hillman, Sidney (Box 220)
  - Smith, Edwin W. (Box 220)
  - Future amendments (Box 220)
  - Committee Reports, Statements, etc. (Box 220)
  - Jay Franklin article, N.L.R.B. (Box 220)
  - Dr. John A. Lapp (Box 220)
  - Miscellaneous cases (Box 220)
  - "The People's Platform", Feb. 7, 1941 [a radio program on which the Judge appeared] (Box 220)
  - Speech before U.S. Chamber of Commerce, [1 May 1940] (Box 220)
  - Chicago speech [Chicago Employers Association, 13 November 1940] (Box 220)
  - Speech - N.Y. State Chamber of Commerce, 6 February 1940 (Box 220)
  - Speech - Birmingham, Alabama [ Associated Industries of Alabama, 10 April 1941] (Box 220)
  - Speech - New York [Chicago] - National Metal Trades Association [ca. 7 May 1941] (Box 220)
  - Article - Virginia Law Review (Box 220)
  - Meetings of the Committee (Box 220)
  - American Forum of the Air, 8 December 1940 (Box 220)
  - Article on War Industries in Town Meeting, March 23, 1941 (Box 220)